[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
What's this sound I'm hearing
with my keen ears?
Sure, I've got good hearing,
but that's not the point here.
It's the sound of desire, of course
-Coming from deep down inside
-My lord.
Who could that be?
Isn't that the young master
who was looking for his cousin?
I was mistaken.
I never imagined you would be
-so well-endowed.
-Goodness!
-You know nothing at all!
-Don't be silly, please.
Listen I'll show you how it's done
What is big and long
May not be the best
A hand plow when you dig for clams
Is better than a pickaxe!
Don't go tossing your pail in a stream
Just blow gently
Put your lips down
Suck, suck, suck
Hey now, Director,
will you stop teasing us like that?
Huh? A waterwheel?
Slosh and…
Squishing here, squishing there
Thump and thud
It digs mighty well
You must hold a flower gently.
Hold it too tight, and it will break.
At this rate, the iron will never get hot.
Planning to dig in dry ground?
Would you care to check
for yourself, young master?
That's right, is it going in?
Let's check
It's going in
For the pestle's standing
Tall and hard
And is going up, going down
All over again
It's going in
Splash! Trickle!
Squeaky here, squeaky there
Thump and thud
It pounds mighty well
Well, that young master
Is nowhere to be found at all
We should not be doing this here.
In time or space
In a palanquin
Swaying, bouncing
Heaving and bobbing
Let's check
It's going in
"My lord,
just how many women have you seduced?"
Do you keep track…
of how many grapes you've eaten?
Well now,
a wise answer to a foolish question.
"So of course I've heard the rumors,
but I never imagined you this lewd."
And those whispers…
What were they?
Goodness, you don't even know.
"They say
you're a gentleman of the night."
A gentleman of the night?
Right
Not just a gentleman, but a saintly one
If he is truly that…
takes great delight in meeting talent
wherever he goes
and then offering them his guidance.
And tonight, I shall…
take great delight in giving you guidance
as a gentleman always should.
Now, this is the teaching of Xunzi.
Drift and glide Like floating along
Like strolling along
On feathery clouds
Then suddenly you go crashing down
Is this a dream?
Ah
Did you just wake me up?
Vanishing just like bubbles
It can never be captured
Like a fleeting shadow
It goes around and brings you right back
-To where you just started
-Cousin!
Dear cousin!
-Dear cousin!
-It's love
Cousin!
-Cousin!
What is this love?
A love that haunts me even in dreams
This love
Also when I'm awake
It is so cruel
Why are you holding me back?
This love
My love
Sweet love of mine…
I'm sure you've heard
from the Left State Councilor already,
but I…
I shall be staying up here for a while.
Nevertheless, whatever the reasons are,
I guess it's fate.
Eun-sil, please say that's all I can hear.
-My lady says she--
-I do regret that I didn't say farewell
the last time we were together.
I was merely wondering
if you had returned home safely.
But if you turn away from me,
what choice have I got left?
Or did you not understand me?
Tell him there is no misunderstanding.
My lady says there is no misunderstanding.
The first time I saw you,
I found this where you'd been standing,
my lady.
I shall accept your thanks
in the form of a letter addressed to me.
There are many ears
and many eyes about us.
He praised your cousin
in truly effusive ways.
For a man of so few words, that is.
My lady. My lady!
Madam is approaching.
This will be the death of me.
Please, my lord, don't do this.
Please give it to me.
My lady.
Oh, he's precocious,
-but very delightful as well.
-All right.
Lady of the First Rank.
Oh, my dear. You're here.
I saw you from afar
and I almost spilled over in delight.
Come, let's go now.
I can't wait for today's poetry reading.
Should you not feel up to it,
I shall be glad to write to you first.
You will do it, won't you?
Yes, I will. Please make haste.
Right here.
Are you unsettled?
I was on my way to the rear garden
with the lady,
and when I saw you like this,
I came to see.
You need not worry.
I'm quite sure the lady noticed nothing.
You can tell me anything and everything.
I humbly apologize. The truth is, I…
I should've come to you straightaway
to thank you
for what you did for me last time.
Please forgive my tardiness.
I can just feel the heartbeat of a mother.
Oh, then this time,
I shall read a poem I have prepared.
"My lover has not yet returned
Though the full moon is waning now
The endless sound of the loom
Fills my lonely heart"
Well, were you attempting
to avoid me again
because you were lonely?
How are you getting along?
I must say it's easy.
So much so, I almost feel sorry for you.
You're in good spirits.
You must remember,
when the task is near completion,
to stop by for a visit, won't you?
Why?
Are you thinking of rehearsing
before I receive just compensation?
It would perhaps be better
if you stopped by during the night.
I tremble with anticipation.
Uh-uh-uh.
Here we are.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Here they are.
Huh.
You have worked very hard
on copying the chapter
on the introduction to Confucian learning.
"A young woman,
upon reaching ten years of age,
should come and go modestly.
At 15, she should put her hair up
with a binyeo.
And before turning 20,
she should be married."
That is correct.
Like a flower, she should bloom.
Yes, indeed.
Go on, take it. Take it.
Come on, take it. It's all right.
Come, come!
Your lady has promised to write back.
-Have you forgotten who you are?
-There, there.
It's all right. Take it, hmm?
Son of a…
It is written that a husband
may take a second wife,
but there is no mention of a wife
taking a second husband.
If one's conduct is at odds
with the will of heaven and earth,
the heaven's punishment shall rain down.
I have duly received your reply.
Thanks to you,
this has been an informative time
in which I could learn the kind of things
ladies study and memorize.
If one's conduct is at odds
with the spirits of heaven and earth,
the heaven's punishment shall rain down.
If there is fault
in a woman's manners and loyalty…
I saw a pair of cuckoos
in the rear garden.
The male and female were sitting
side by side, singing so sweetly.
As I stood there, enraptured,
listening to the noble song of love
sung by such lovely creatures,
I couldn't help but feel jealous.
If one's conduct is at odds
with the spirits of heaven and earth,
the heaven's punishment shall rain down.
If there is fault
in a woman's manners and loyalty,
her husband will soon treat her coldly.
Eun-sil…
Eun-sil, stop making that racket.
Hmm.
Yesterday, I took a walk
with Young Master In-ho,
and we discussed many things.
I did not probe any further, though,
for fear the young master's
feelings might be hurt.
But it seems he feels the absence
of his late brother quite acutely.
Lord.
My lord.
I am aware I am overstepping,
but I wished
that I could help fill that void,
however modestly.
If one's conduct is at odds
with the spirits of heaven and earth,
the heaven's punishment will rain down.
If there is fault
in a woman's manners and loyalty,
her husband will soon treat her coldly.
Oh my.
What'd you say your name was again?
You remember, don't you?
Chil-seong. It's Chil-seong.
I'm very insulted.
Like "Seven Names"?
A fitting name for a servant.
Ah, not so.
When I was an infant,
I was known as Container.
Then it was Dog Balls a while.
Then Straw Mat, you know? Meongseok.
'Cause I was beaten by a straw mat.
How can that make you laugh?
Anyway, who gave you
the name of Chil-seong?
Cho Won.
Lord Cho Won.
I have served seven masters in all.
A different family name
for each one that I served.
Which is why I'm Chil-seong,
"Seven Names."
Imploring that the Chos
would be my last master.
With that name,
I couldn't be sold to anyone else.
It's been a difficult life
for you as well.
Wait, move aside.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear. This…
Oh, my God.
You might have taken care of this.
I…
My lady.
Who's there?
Who else? It's Eun-sil.
I have something for you.
Where on earth have you been?
There's a letter for you.
A letter?
If one's conduct is at odds
with the spirits of heaven and earth,
the heaven's punishment shall rain down.
If there is fault
in a woman's manners and loyalty…
Here. Insert this and deliver it to her.
Huh?
Hmm…
Right.
I shall prepare a concoction
of pomegranate and velvet antler.
Please make sure she drinks it
before going to bed.
To ensure your body
is in child bearing condition,
you must be sure to take it
every single day.
I am grateful, my lord. Thank you so much.
You should be thanking my lady.
Isn't that right, my lady?
Keep a fair countenance
and hold fast to your virtue.
Conduct yourself with modesty
-and decorum, and serve your husband.
-Replying to a blank letter, huh?
She isn't even reading them, is she?
Oh my. Aren't you pretty?
My lady, how about this one?
Do you even read…
all the letters I've been sending?
How can you possibly be so impolite?
Without even bothering to see or read
what is in my heart, you send a reply?
My lord…
have you not ignored the many requests
that I've earnestly made?
All the while,
I have kept every one of my promises.
Have you no pity for my aching heart?
Hmm.
Tie it securely.
Take those. You can take those with you.
Heave ho.
Hmm.
Mother.
I shall very shortly be at your side,
dear husband.
Take it easy.
Dear me, we didn't know
the elders of this household left
for the end of the mourning period
and brought along this precious alcohol!
Huh?
So now, what do I do with this?
-Oh my.
-What is it? Alcohol?
Hey!
-Here we go.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, come on!
What do you think you're doing?
Chil-seong,
I didn't take you for such a man.
What am I supposed to do?
Should I just disobey orders
from my lord? Can I?
Everyone, look at this!
This piece of land
will be quite fertile next year,
so you can plant whatever you want.
-Hey, hey, hey, hey! Hey! Hey!
-Don't do that!
That's precious!
Why would he tell you to throw it away?
Hurry up, hurry up!
Continue as your lord commanded.
Keep throwing it away!
-Throw it away? Wait, should I?
-Come on! Here. Pour it off into this.
Throw it away by pouring it off here.
You're not disobeying.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Throwing it away.
We have some leftovers for the
ancestral rites in the kitchen, don't we?
Hey, Chil-seong!
You're a right good scoundrel
of a servant!
-Wait, stop!
-Hey, Chil-seong!
You're a right good scoundrel
of a servant!
Stop wasting it!
This is…
With a face like this, really.
And I've added so much sweet tenderness.
What else could you ask of me then, huh?
Your reply is duly received.
Your handwriting is as beautiful…
You are shameless and inconsiderate.
I can scarcely believe
you've written me again
even after my preposterous reply.
Why on earth do you torment me so?
Yesterday, I took a walk
with Young Master In-ho.
We conversed on many topics.
I was sure I judged you correctly.
Deep in your heart, my lord,
there is such gentleness,
such considerate regard.
But for some unknown reason,
when you say you wish to help
fill that void for the young master,
I grow jealous of him.
Surely I deserve to die
for having such thoughts.
My lord, whom I miss so dearly.
Appear before my eyes, I pray you.
My heart is in turmoil,
and sleep has utterly forsaken me.
Please appear before me,
if only in dreams.
Eun-sil, are you there?
Eun-sil.
Don't be alarmed, my lady.
It is I, Cho Won.
I have come here to see you.
What peculiar words you speak, sir.
Please leave at once.
Then I shall pretend
this whole thing never happened.
Do you mean to say
that you did not wish to see me?
How could one so well-versed
in duty and propriety
ask me such
an embarrassing question as that?
Have I heard you right?
Do you consider me an embarrassment then?
I have learned over time
that your heart resembles mine.
So however could I not?
However could I not have come to see you?
Isn't that why…
you have deigned to respond
to the letters I sent?
I…
have seen every single one
of your replies.
Don't do this, my lord. I'm begging you.
Why must you be so cruel to me?
How can you aspire so earnestly to a fate…
that cannot be in this life?
If not in this life…
then in the next…
could you and I be together?
If so, then I beg you…
…send me to my next life right now.
If you can't oblige…
then there is no other choice.
We shall be together in this life.
Just as we are now.
Tonight, I am certain…
in our dreams, we shall meet.
I can swear to that.
She's falling for it so easily,
it's almost disappointing.
She might cry herself to sleep, I daresay.
Madam.
Lord Cho Won is here.
You told me to come
when I felt it was almost done.
So despite the lateness of the hour…
I couldn't help but come.
My apologies, cousin.
Well, I see you're optimistic
about your success.
I have just now been with the young widow.
Just the two of us alone.
Most… discreetly.
How very ingenious you are.
There must have been
at least ten pairs of eyes observing.
Yes, but what have I to fear
when I am guided by such clear intent?
Especially now that the woman,
once biting and distant,
is nestled in my arms so very sweetly?
Nestled?
The young widow?
Isn't this her first time
in a man's embrace?
She's all but melted in my arms.
Honestly, I could not help but smile.
Until tonight,
I had been acting as planned in advance.
But now, I've…
nearly been found out.
Nearly found out?
-On what score?
-Oh, I think you know.
All this gaudy tomfoolery I indulge in.
So what did you do then?
You've made me most curious
to know the details.
If I could be with you in our next life,
then I would like to…
move on to that next life without delay.
After all this time,
I finally encounter a man
who leaves me breathless.
These hands of yours, strong and thick,
how I've missed holding them so close.
Just as I…
every single day…
have missed the sound
of your sweet breath.
As I'm listening to this,
I know these words will get me wet
and keep me wet all night.
"Again and again, my legs keep spreading,
but I have no husband to fill the void"…
These hands of yours,
strong and thick, how I've missed them.
"Come here, very close,
and scold my womanhood most moist,
I beg of you."
"Bun-hui"?
Hmm.
So why…
Why is it that you only
brush her shoulders and then stopped?
It's from So-ok's mother.
The one who sells tobacco.
Ladies who can't get me out of their heads
are abundant across the nation.
All eight provinces, I'm sure.
She is just one of them.
As you must be aware,
if there's one thing a woman hates,
it's talk of other women one has seen.
Wait a second.
Have I been upsetting you so much now?
Well, then.
You still have the remnants
of a bitter smile on your brow.
It would not do
for me to try to imitate it for you.
Well, by way of apology,
I shall entrust this letter to you,
dear cousin.
I'm sure you'll find greater use for it
than I.
I'm talking about the daughter
of the woman who wrote this, of course.
Use this to teach her.
I'm sure there's no better way
to make her a good concubine.
Reciting this, as is,
will make my brother-in-law
a happy man indeed.
Count on me then.
I shall put your apology to good use.
I think someone else
may need it more than So-ok.
I could give it to the young widow,
wouldn't that be kind?
Ah. It is mine now,
so your opinion about it isn't necessary.
Oh, no.
I'm seeing you swallowing
and gulping so nervously.
I can only assume that you're flustered.
Oh, dear.
It would not do
for me to try to imitate it for you.
On the contrary.
It's just,
I'm imagining how that young widow,
upon reading this letter,
will react to my manhood.
Oh, yes, do you think
she'll lose consciousness?
Gye-hwa,
would you possibly be outside?
Did you call for me, ma'am?
Go see the Left State Councilor's
daughter-in-law at once
and bring her this letter.
Gye-hwa.
Did you hear me? What did I say?
Sorry, ma'am.
I will open the door now.
I do wonder how the young widow will react
to the letter when she reads it.
If you bid me to cease at once,
I could still stop that letter
from reaching the young widow's eyes.
Just say the word.
What shall I do…
dear cousin?
Let's see what happens.
Let's push it to the end.
Where is… Ah.
Here it is.
You there!
You're Gye-hwa, are you not?
Yes, I am, madam.
Come quickly.
So, in the middle of the night,
she sent you here
with something belonging to Geum-ho,
is that right?
Yes, madam.
She said it was precious and that
I should deliver it here right away.
Ah, very well.
Ganghwa,
you take it for now,
give it to Hui-yeon at daybreak.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that a tobacco container?
How considerate she is.
With all this happening,
she even thought of me.
Take it and go inside.
Yes, madam.
You may go. You're dismissed.
Sorry.
Madam. It is I, Gye-hwa.
May I have your leave to enter?
I humbly apologize, madam.
The Lady of the First Rank…
…took the tobacco box.
What about the letter that was in the box?
That too.
This is my fault.
Please do not forgive me.
I will accept any punishment.
Gye-hwa.
Yes, ma'am.
When have I ever punished you
for anything at all?
Let us send my lady a present,
and let's make it something fitting.